<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="text">
        <item>Whoever fasts Ramadhan and follows it with six days of Shawwal, it will be as if he fasted for a lifetime.</item>
        <item>Ibn Abbas (ra) said that the Messenger of Allah (saw) said regarding laylatul Qadr, It is pleasant and clear, neither hot nor cold, the sun rises in the morning with a weak red (colour).</item>
        <item>The Night of Decree is better than a thousand months. The angels and the Spirit descend therein by permission of their Lord for every matter. Peace it is until the emergence of dawn.</item>
        <item>It was narrated from Aishah that she said, O Messenger of Allah, what do you think I should say in my supplication, if I come upon Laylatul-Qadr? He said, Say O Allah, You are Forgiving and love forgiveness, so forgive me.</item>
        <item>The month of Ramadan to the other months is like Yusuf (as) to his brothers. So, just like Yusuf (as) was the most beloved son to Yaqub (as), Ramadan is likewise the most beloved month to Allah (swt).</item>
        <item>The Prophet (saw) said, The people will remain upon goodness as long as they hasten to break their fast.</item>
        <item>And it is the month of sabr, and for sabr, the reward is paradise.</item>
        <item>Fasting is half of sabr (patience).</item>
        <item>O Allah bless us in Rajab and Shaban and let us reach Ramadan.</item>
        <item>The Prophet Muhammad (saw) said, If any Muslim comes out of Ramadan without gaining forgiveness and goodness, he is a real loser.</item>
        <item>Allah is the greatest. O Allah, let the crescent loom above us in safety, imaan, peace, and Islam, and in agreement with all that You love and pleases You. Our Lord and your Lord is Allah.</item>
        <item>Uthman said, I heard the Messenger of Allah (saw) say: Fasting is a shield against the Fire just like the shield of anyone of you against fighting.</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, decreed upon you is fasting as it was decreed upon those before you that you may become righteous.</item>
        <item>Abu Hurairah narrated that the Messenger of Allah (saw) said, When you see the new crescent then fast, and when you see it then stop fasting. If it is cloudy then fast thirty days.</item>
        <item>Abu Huraira narrated that, Allah\'s Messenger (saw) said, When Ramadan begins, the gates of Paradise are opened.</item>
        <item>The Prophet (saw) used to strive hard (in ibaadah [worship]) in the last ten nights of ramadan as he never did at any other time.</item>
        <item>Whoever fasts ramadan out of imaan and the hope of reward will be forgiven his previous sins.</item>
        <item>The month of Ramadan is superior to all other months, and the last ten nights are superior to the other nights.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>